Guide to the Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
Bambaataa, Afrika hip hop archive,
- Series IX. Music Collection
  - 12 inch Vinyl
    - Not annotated
      - F
        - Fiasco, Lupe - Lupe Fiasco's food and liquor (Disc one), 2006; SR-15273; Fiasco, Lupe (Box 265)
          In same jacket as # SR-15274. Double album.
          Catalog # 83959-1; A-side Matrix # ST-A-83959A-1
        - Fiasco, Lupe - Lupe Fiasco's food and liquor (Disc two), 2006; SR-15274; Fiasco, Lupe (Box 265)
          In same jacket as # SR-15273. Double album.
          Catalog # 83959-1; A-side Matrix # ST-A-83959C-1
        - Fiasco, Lupe - Lupe Fiasco's food and liquor (Disc one), 2006; SR-15275; Fiasco, Lupe (Box 265)
          In same jacket as # SR-15276. Double album.
        - Fiasco, Lupe - Lupe Fiasco's food and liquor (Disc two), 2006; SR-15276; Fiasco, Lupe (Box 265)
          In same jacket as # SR-15275. Double album.
        - Fiasco, Lupe - Kick push; Just might be okay, 2006; SR-15277; Fiasco, Lupe (Box 265)
        - Fidelfatti - Listen to my music, 1991; SR-15278; Fidelfatti; Shirley (Box 265)
          Catalog # NMX 520; A-side Matrix # NMX 520 A
          New Music International
          Milan, Italy
        - Fidelfatti - Just wanna touch me, 1989; SR-15279; Fidelfatti; Ronnette (Box 265)
          Catalog # URBXR 46; A-side Matrix # URBXR46 A-2U-1-1
          Urban
        - Fielder, Arthur - Saturday night Fielder, 1978; SR-15280; Fielder, Arthur; Boston Pops Orchestra (Box 265)
          Catalog # MSI-011; A-side Matrix # MSI-011-A A. FIELDER
        - Field Mob - Project dreamz, 2000; SR-15281; Field Mob (Box 265)
          Catalog # MCAR 25136-1; A-side Matrix # MCA 13743
          MCA Records
          Santa Monica, California
        - Fields, Alvin - Special delivery, 1981; SR-15282; Fields, Alvin (Box 265)
          Catalog # SP-17190; A-side Matrix # A&M SPO17190-A
        - Fields, Lizz - When I see love; Say the word (Remixes), 2004; SR-15283; Fields, Lizz (Box 265)
          Catalog # USEXY12 001; A-side Matrix # 08 53711 20 1A1
          Unisex
        - Fields, Richard "Dimples" - Your wife is cheatin' on us, 1984; SR-15284; Fields, Richard "Dimples" (Box 265)
          Catalog # JD-13831; A-side Matrix # PD 13831A 5
          RCA
        - Fiend - Talk it like I bring it, 1999; SR-15285; Fiend (Box 265)
          Catalog # SPRO 81232; A-side Matrix # 08724-81232-1A
          No Limit Records
          Richmond, California
        - Fiend - Big timer, 1998; SR-15286; Fiend (Box 265)
          Catalog # SPRO 81105; A-side Matrix # SPRO-81105-A
        - Fifth Dimension - Surrender, 1983; SR-15287; Fifth Dimension (Box 265)
          Catalog # SUD 013; A-side Matrix # SUD-013-A
        - Figures on a beach - Swimming, 1983; SR-15288; Figures on a beach (Box 265)
          Catalog # MA-1003; A-side Matrix # MA-1003-A
          Metro-America
        - File 13 - Taste so good, 1984; SR-15289; File 13 (Box 265)
          Catalog # PRO-7052 DJ; A-side Matrix # PRO-7052-A
          Profile Records
        - Filter - Where do we go from here (Disc one), 2002; SR-15290; Filter (Box 265)
          In same jacket as # SR-15291. Double album.
          Catalog # PRO-A-100898; A-side Matrix # 0-42444-A/PRO-A-100898-A-SR-1
        - Filter - Where do we go from here (Disc two), 2002; SR-15291; Filter (Box 265)
          In same jacket as # SR-15290. Double album.
          Catalog # PRO-A-100898; A-side Matrix # 0-42444-C/PRO-A-100898-C-SR-1
        - Fine Young Cannibals - Johnny come home, 1985; SR-15292; Fine Young Cannibals (Box 265)
          Catalog # 882 062-1; A-side Matrix # 261 882062 1 // 1 380 POLYGRAPH
        - Finesse - Feel it, 1982; SR-15293; Finesse (Box 265)
          Catalog # 44-02978; A-side Matrix # XSS170177-1A
        - Finesse - I can't help myself, 1985; SR-15294; Finesse (Box 265)
          Catalog # 880 946-1; A-side Matrix # 880-946-1-2-58423-ALD-2
          Mercury
        - Finesse & Synquis - I'll be there, 1988; SR-15295; Finesse & Synquis; Finesse (Box 265)
          Catalog # MCA-23893; A-side Matrix # MCA 8184 FW2
        - Finesse & Synquis - Soul sisters; Soft but deadly, 1988; SR-15296; Finesse & Synquis; Finesse (Box 265)
          Catalog # MCA-23849; A-side Matrix # MCA-7661-FW2
        - Fingall, Mac - Come go with me, 1995; SR-15297; Fingall, Mac (Box 265)
          Catalog # BF-048; A-side Matrix # MACFINGALL-95-A
          Bayfield
          Barbados
        - Fingathing - Check it out, 2001; SR-15298; Fingathing (Box 265)
          Catalog # GC 141; A-side Matrix # GC-141-A
          Grand Central Records
        - Fingathing - Walk in space, 2004; SR-15299; Fingathing (Box 265)
          Catalog # GC 182; A-side Matrix # GC-182A-1
        - Fingertapp - You can't talk about love, 2003; SR-15300; Fingertapp; Fernandez, Hazel (Box 265)
          Catalog # GRAPE 003; A-side Matrix # GRAPE 003 A
          Grape Records
        - Finn, Mickey - When the morning comes, 2002; SR-15301; Finn, Mickey; L.Double (Box 265)
          Catalog # URBTAKE 32; A-side Matrix # URBTAKE32A
          Urban Takeover
        - Fiorello - Azzurro, 2000; SR-15302; Fiorello (Box 265)
          Test pressing
          Catalog # RISE 090; A-side Matrix # RISE 090 A
          Rise
        - Fire and Ice - Inferno (Burn baby burn), 1979; SR-15303; Fire and Ice (Box 265)
          In same jacket as # SR-15304. 2 copies.
          Catalog # FLY-13947; A-side Matrix # MCA 1892 W1
          Butterfly Records
        - Fire and Ice - Inferno (Burn baby burn), 1979; SR-15304; Fire and Ice (Box 265)
          In same jacket as # SR-15303. 2 copies.
        - Fire On Blonde - Bounce back, 1987; SR-15305; Fire On Blonde (Box 265)
          Catalog # DMD 1168; A-side Matrix # ST DM 54566-54564-1
        - Fire On Blonde - Stop and think, 1986; SR-15306; Fire On Blonde (Box 265)
          Catalog # DMD 946; A-side Matrix # ST-DM-49691-1
        - Fired-Up Krew - Don't burn me up, 2000; SR-15307; Fired-Up Krew (Box 265)
          Catalog # DDR 004; A-side Matrix # DDR 004-A
          Dig Deep Records
        - Firefly - Firefly, 1980; SR-15308; Firefly (Box 265)
          Catalog # MD 8025; A-side Matrix # Piero
          Mr. Disco Organization
        - Firefly - Love (Is gonna be on your side), 1981; SR-15309; Firefly (Box 265)
          Catalog # EMDS 6515; A-side Matrix # EMDS-6515-A
          Emergency Records
        - Firefly - Stay, 1985; SR-15310; Firefly (Box 265)
          Catalog # EMDS 6549; A-side Matrix # EMDS-6549-A
        - Firefox - Who is it, 1996; SR-15311; Firefox; Suvivor (Box 266)
          Catalog # PB009; A-side Matrix # PB-009 AA
          Philly Blunt Records
        - Firestarr - Dying for rap, 2000; SR-15312; Firestarr; Starr, Fredro (Box 266)
          Catalog # KOC-PRO-1043; A-side Matrix # 25-KOC-PRO1054-1 A
          Koch Records
        - Firestarters - Melodicy, 2004; SR-15313; Firestarters; Publik; Jae Saunt (Box 266)
          Catalog # unknown; A-side Matrix # VN 001 A
          Various Notes Records
        - First Choice - Let no man put asunder, 1993; SR-15314; First Choice; Fleming, Rochelle (Box 266)
          Catalog # 2571-1; A-side Matrix # 5599-1-A
          Salsoul Records
        - First Choice - Doctor love (Special remix), 1983; SR-15315; First Choice; Fleming, Rochelle (Box 266)
          Catalog # SG 419 DJ; A-side Matrix # SG-419-A
        - First Choice - Delusions, 1977; SR-15316; First Choice (Box 266)
          Catalog # CPLP 8060; A-side Matrix # CPLP 8060 A
          Charly Records
        - First Circle - Workin' up a sweat, 1986; SR-15317; First Circle (Box 266)
          Catalog # V-19236; A-side Matrix # V-1-19236-Z2
          EMI America
        - First Circle - Miracle worker, 1987; SR-15318; First Circle (Box 266)
          Catalog # V-19253; A-side Matrix # V-1-19253-Z1
        - First Down - Let the battle begin, 1993; SR-15319; First Down (Box 266)
          Catalog # FD 002; A-side Matrix # FD-002-A1
          Ill Gotten Gains!
        - First Down - Mad dogs and Englishmen.. E.P., 1994; SR-15320; First Down (Box 266)
          Catalog # BV 1008-1; A-side Matrix # EFA 61008-A 13V 1008-1 A
          Blitz Vinyl
          Dusseldorf, Germany
        - First Draft - Too many people, 2004; SR-15321; First Draft (Box 266)
          Catalog # FDO-10504; A-side Matrix # FDO-10504A
        - First Frontal Assault - Bloodfire Assault, 1991; SR-15322; First Frontal Assault (Box 266)
          Catalog # NOTE 56 DJ; A-side Matrix # NOTE-56-A
          Music of Life
        - First Love - Give me your love, 1985; SR-15323; First Love (Box 266)
          Catalog # DMD 867; A-side Matrix # ST-DM 48219-1
          Mirage
        - First Love - It's a mystery to me, 1982; SR-15324; First Love (Box 266)
          Catalog # 4Z9 03422; A-side Matrix # 4Z9-03422-3-AB
          Chicago International Music (C.I.M.)
        - First Love - Don't say goodnight; Love me today, 1980; SR-15325; First Love (Box 266)
          In same jacket as # SR-15326. 2 copies. Annotated.
          Catalog # DK 100; A-side Matrix # DK100-1-200-1E
          Dakar Records
        - First Love - Don't say goodnight; Love me today, 1980; SR-15326; First Love (Box 266)
          In same jacket as # SR-15325. 2 copies.
        - Darcadian - State of emergency, 2002; SR-15327; Darcadian (Box 266)
          In same jacket as # SR-15328. Different discs.
          Catalog # FIF011; A-side Matrix # 0207x31-A
          First in Flight
          Manchester, United Kingdom
        - Filterheadz - The Rhythm; Protection, 2003; SR-15328; Filterheadz; Tomaz (Box 266)
          In same jacket as # SR-15327. Different discs.
          Catalog # PB3016; A-side Matrix # 08 49900 20 1A1 PB 3016
          Pitch Black
        - Fisher, Cevin - Dangerous disco: the adventures of Double O Cevin (Disc one), 1999; SR-15329; Fisher, Cevin (Box 266)
          In same jacket as # SR-15330; SR-15331. Triple album.
          Catalog # UNDJ A LP 011; A-side Matrix # UAV-002-A
          DMC
        - Fisher, Cevin - Dangerous disco: the adventures of Double O Cevin (Disc two), 1999; SR-15330; Fisher, Cevin (Box 266)
          In same jacket as # SR-15329; SR-15331. Triple album.
          Catalog # UNDJ A LP 011; A-side Matrix # UAV-002-C
        - Fisher, Cevin - Dangerous disco: the adventures of Double O Cevin (Disc three), 1999; SR-15331; Fisher, Cevin (Box 266)
          In same jacket as # SR-15329; SR-15330. Triple album.
          Catalog # UNDJ A LP 011; A-side Matrix # UAV-002-E
        - Fisher, Climie - Rise to the occasion (Hip hop remix), 1987; SR-15332; Fisher, Climie (Box 266)
          Catalog # 1C K 060-20 2184 6; A-side Matrix # 2021846-A1
        - Fisher, Climie - Everything, 1987; SR-15333; Fisher, Climie (Box 266)
          Catalog # EMC 3538; A-side Matrix # EMC 3538 A-2-1-
        - Fisher, Climie - Love changes (Everything), 1988; SR-15334; Fisher, Climie (Box 266)
          Catalog # V-15373; A-side Matrix # V-1-15373-X601450-B & X601450
        - Fit - Under your spell, 1988; SR-15335; Fit (Box 266)
          Catalog # SP-12275; A-side Matrix # AM SP 012275-A-ES1
        - Fitzgerald, Ella - The best of Ella Fitzgerald (Disc one), 1962; SR-15336; Fitzgerald, Ella (Box 266)
          In same jacket as # SR-15337. Double album.
          Catalog # DXSB-7156; A-side Matrix # 7 6368 1
          Decca
        - Fitzgerald, Ella - The best of Ella Fitzgerald (Disc two), 1962; SR-15337; Fitzgerald, Ella (Box 266)
          In same jacket as # SR-15336. Double album.
          Catalog # DXSB-7156; A-side Matrix # 7 6369 1
        - Fitzgerald, Ella - Ella and Louis again (Disc one), 1957; SR-15338; Fitzgerald, Ella; Armstrong, Louis (Box 266)
          In same jacket as # SR-15339. Double album.
          Catalog # MGV 4006-2; A-side Matrix # MGV-4006-2 Side-1 50,392
          Verve Records
        - Fitzgerald, Ella - Ella and Louis again (Disc two), 1957; SR-15339; Fitzgerald, Ella; Armstrong, Louis (Box 266)
          In same jacket as # SR-15338. Double album.
          Catalog # MGV 4006-2; A-side Matrix # MGV-4006-2 Side-3 50,394
        - Fitzgerald, Ella - Sings the Rodgers and Hart song book (Disc one), 1956; SR-15340; Fitzgerald, Ella (Box 266)
          In same jacket as # SR-15341. Double album.
          Catalog # MGV-4002-2; A-side Matrix # MGV-4002-Side-1 50134-1
        - Fitzgerald, Ella - Sings the Rodgers and Hart song book (Disc two), 1956; SR-15341; Fitzgerald, Ella (Box 266)
          In same jacket as # SR-15340. Double album.
          Catalog # MGV-4002-2; A-side Matrix # MGV-4002-Side-3 50136-1A
        - Fitzgerald, Ella - Ella Fitzgerald sings the Cole Porter Songbook (Disc one), 1956; SR-15657; Fitzgerald, Ella (Box 266)
          In same jacket as # SR-15658. Double album.
          Catalog # MGV-4001-2; A-side Matrix # MGV-4001-2-S1
        - Fitzgerald, Ella - Ella fitzgerald sings the Cole Porter Songbook (Disc two), 1956; SR-15658; Fitzgerald, Ella (Box 266)
          In same jacket as # SR-15657. Double album.
          Catalog # MGV-4001-2; A-side Matrix # MGV-4001-2-S3
        - Fitzi Niceness - Proposal, 1996; SR-15659; Fitzi Niceness (Box 266)
          Catalog # MST013; A-side Matrix # MST-013-A
          Madstorm Production
          Dorchester, Massachusetts
        - Five Special - Trak'n, 1981; SR-15660; Five Special (Box 266)
          Catalog # 5E-553; A-side Matrix # 5E-553-A-SH-2AR
        - Five Star - Let me be the one, 1985; SR-15661; Five Star (Box 266)
          Catalog # JW-14230; A-side Matrix # PW 14230A 1
        - Five Star - Can't wait another minute, 1986; SR-15662; Five Star (Box 266)
          Catalog # JD-14422; A-side Matrix # PW-14422A-2
        - Five Star - Someone's in love, 1988; SR-15663; Five Star (Box 266)
          Catalog # 8712-1-RDAC; A-side Matrix # 8712-1-RD-A
        - Fixx - Phantoms, 1984; SR-15664; Fixx (Box 266)
          Catalog # MCA-5507; A-side Matrix # MCA4508-SS9
        - Fixx - Built for the future, 1986; SR-15665; Fixx (Box 266)
          Catalog # L33-17181; A-side Matrix # MCA-5979-SS2
        - Flack, Roberta - The best of, SR-15666; Flack, Roberta (Box 266)
          Catalog # HP-044; A-side Matrix # HP-044-A
          House Party
        - Flack, Roberta - Roberta Flack, 1978; SR-15667; Flack, Roberta (Box 266)
          Catalog # SD 19168; A-side Matrix # STA-784131-H
        - Flairck - Circus, 1981; SR-15668; Flairck (Box 266)
          Catalog # 2925 122; A-side Matrix # 2925 122 1Y 1
        - Flakes - Sugar frosted lover, 1980; SR-15669; Flakes (Box 266)
          In same jacket as # SR-15670. 2 copies.
          Catalog # MD 1980; A-side Matrix # MD-1980-A
          Magic Discs Records
        - Flakes - Sugar frosted lover, 1980; SR-15670; Flakes (Box 266)
          In same jacket as # SR-15669. 2 copies.
        - Flakes - Flakes I - 1980, 1980; SR-15671; Flakes (Box 266)
          Catalog # MDLP-118; A-side Matrix # MD-LP-118-B
        - FlamBey - That's what she's lookin' for, 2003; SR-15672; FlamBey (Box 266)
          Catalog # unknown; A-side Matrix # BE-101-A-REV
          Bright Vision Entertainment
        - Flames - Soca and Dancehall Remix, 1995; SR-15673; Flames; Bajja Jedd; Burning Flames (Box 266)
          In same jacket as # SR-15674. 2 copies. Annotated.
          Catalog # BF 014A; A-side Matrix # BFX-014-A
          Burning Flames Music
          Antigua
        - Flames - Soca and Dancehall Remix, 1995; SR-15674; Flames; Bajja Jedd; Burning Flames (Box 266)
          In same jacket as # SR-15673. 2 copies.
        - Flash and the Pan - Waiting for a train, 1982; SR-15675; Flash and the Pan (Box 266)
          Catalog # 49-03546; A-side Matrix # XSS-170748-1B
        - Flat Bed Ford - Green for go, 1998; SR-15676; Flat Bed Ford (Box 266)
          In same jacket as # SR-15677. 2 copies.
          Catalog # Tree 015; A-side Matrix # TREE-015-A
          Tree Records
          Orlando, Florida
        - Flat Bed Ford - Green for go, 1998; SR-15677; Flat Bed Ford (Box 266)
          In same jacket as # SR-15676. 2 copies.
        - Flavor - In good taste, 1976; SR-15678; Flavor (Box 266)
          Catalog # JP6-1002S1; A-side Matrix # JP6-1002S1-2705-S-06B
          Ju-Par Records
        - Flavour - Mandolay, 1987; SR-15679; Flavour (Box 266)
          Catalog # 91935; A-side Matrix # 91935-A
          Seathru Records
        - FLB - Boogie town, 1978; SR-15680; FLB (Box 266)
          Catalog # D-121; A-side Matrix # D-121-A
          Fantasy WMOT Records
        - Fleetwood Mac - Big love, 1987; SR-15681; Fleetwood Mac (Box 267)
          Catalog # 0-20683; A-side Matrix # 0-20683A-SH2
        - Fleetwood Mac - Family man, 1987; SR-15682; Fleetwood Mac (Box 267)
          Catalog # 0-20842; A-side Matrix # 0-20842-A-SR4DMM
        - Fleetwood Mac - Mirage, 1982; SR-15683; Fleetwood Mac (Box 267)
          Catalog # 1-23607; A-side Matrix # B-16832-5-2 1-23607-A-S-2
        - Fleetwood, Mick - The visitor, 1981; SR-15684; Fleetwood, Mick (Box 267)
          In same jacket as # SR-15685. Different discs.
          Catalog # AFL1-4080; A-side Matrix # AFL1-4080-A
          RCA Victor
        - Fleetwood, Mick - The visitor, 1981; SR-15685; Fleetwood, Mick (Box 267)
          In same jacket as # SR-15684. Different discs.
          Catalog # AFL1-4080; A-side Matrix # AFL1-4080A 1
        - Fleming, Rochelle - Suffer! (The consequences) (Disc one), 1995; SR-15686; Fleming, Rochelle (Box 267)
          In same jacket as # SR-15687. Double album.
          Catalog # CR-340; A-side Matrix # CR340-A
          Cutting Records
        - Fleming, Rochelle - Suffer! (The consequences) (Disc two), 1995; SR-15687; Fleming, Rochelle (Box 267)
          In same jacket as # SR-15686. Double album.
          Catalog # CR-340; A-side Matrix # CR340-C
        - Flenoy, Julian - Turn me out, 1985; SR-15688; Flenoy, Julian (Box 267)
          In same jacket as # SR-15689. 2 copies.
          Catalog # KMA-12-005; A-side Matrix # L10514-KMA-12-005-A
          KMA Records
        - Flenoy, Julian - Turn me out, 1985; SR-15689; Flenoy, Julian (Box 267)
          In same jacket as # SR-15688. 2 copies.
        - Flesh - The second choice, 1986; SR-15690; Flesh (Box 267)
          Catalog # LONX 87; A-side Matrix # LONX 87 A//1
        - Flesh For Lulu - I go crazy, 1987; SR-15691; Flesh For Lulu (Box 267)
          Catalog # L33-17280; A-side Matrix # MCA-6626-SS1
        - Flesh For Lulu - I go crazy, 1987; SR-15692; Flesh For Lulu (Box 267)
          Catalog # MCA-23736; A-side Matrix # MCA 6673-ASR1
        - Flesh-N-Bone - World so cruel, 1996; SR-15693; Flesh-N-Bone (Box 267)
          Catalog # DEF 111-1; A-side Matrix # DEF 111-1A
          Def Jam Recordings
        - Flex & Da Boriqua Posse - Shake dat hoochie koochie, 1994; SR-15694; Flex & Da Boriqua Posse (Box 267)
          Catalog # RDAB-62906-1; A-side Matrix # RDAB-62906-1-A1
        - Flightt - She's sexxxy, 1988; SR-15695; Flightt (Box 267)
          Catalog # AIR 002 TR520852; A-side Matrix # TR-520852-A
          Paj Records
          New Jersey
        - Flip Da Scrip - You to me, 1996; SR-15696; Flip Da Scrip (Box 267)
          Catalog # NTR 004 FM; A-side Matrix # NTR-004-A1
          Nightown Records
        - Flip Da Scrip - Everybody funk now, 1996; SR-15697; Flip Da Scrip (Box 267)
          Catalog # NTR 009; A-side Matrix # NTR 009-A1
        - Flip Da Scrip - Throw ya hands in the air '95 (Remixes), 1995; SR-15698; Flip Da Scrip (Box 267)
          Catalog # 8800512; A-side Matrix # NTR-002-A1
        - Flip Da Scrip - Everybody funk now, 1996; SR-15699; Flip Da Scrip (Box 267)
        - Flip Da Scrip - You can run, 1997; SR-15700; Flip Da Scrip (Box 267)
          Catalog # NTR 017; A-side Matrix # NTR-017-A1
        - Flip Squad Allstars - The things I do, 1998; SR-15701; Flip Squad Allstars (Box 267)
          Catalog # MCA 13252; A-side Matrix # MCA-13252
        - Flipmode Squad - Cha cha cha, 1998; SR-15702; Flipmode Squad (Box 267)
          In same jacket as # SR-15703. 2 copies.
          Catalog # ED 6100; A-side Matrix # ST-ED-6100-A-1
        - Flipmode Squad - Cha cha cha, 1998; SR-15703; Flipmode Squad (Box 267)
          In same jacket as # SR-15702. 2 copies.
        - Flipp - Roaches; Gas, 1991; SR-15704; Flipp (Box 267)
          Catalog # MR-50002X; A-side Matrix # MR5-0002-X
          Moon Roof Records
        - Flirtations - Earthquake, 1983; SR-15705; Flirtations (Box 267)
          Catalog # D A-side Matrix # DD-103-A
          D&D Records
        - Flirts - New toy, 1985; SR-15706; Flirts (Box 267)
          Catalog # 4Z9-05334; A-side Matrix # AA-4Z9-05334-4
          CBS Associated Records
        - Flirts - You & me, 1985; SR-15707; Flirts (Box 267)
          Catalog # 4Z9-05284; A-side Matrix # 4Z9-05284-4AA
        - Flirts - Miss you, 1986; SR-15708; Flirts (Box 267)
          Catalog # 4Z9-05914; A-side Matrix # AC 4Z9-05914-4
        - Floaters - Magic (We thank you), 1978; SR-15709; Floaters (Box 267)
          Catalog # DM-13; A-side Matrix # DM-13-SP-DJ-A4-377
          ABC Records
        - Flock of Seagulls - Telecommunication, 1981; SR-15710; Flock of Seagulls (Box 267)
          Catalog # JIVE T 4; A-side Matrix # JIVE-T-4-A2
        - Flock of Seagulls - I ran, 1982; SR-15711; Flock of Seagulls (Box 267)
          Catalog # JIVE T 14; A-side Matrix # JIVE-T-A3
        - Flock of Seagulls - A Flock of Seagulls, 1982; SR-15712; Flock of Seagulls (Box 267)
          Catalog # VA 66000; A-side Matrix # VA66000-SA
        - Floetry - Flo'Ology (Disc one), 2005; SR-15713; Floetry (Box 267)
          In same jacket as # SR-15714. Double album.
          Catalog # GEFF-11613-1; A-side Matrix # GEFR 11614-1 A
          Geffen Records
        - Floetry - Flo'Ology (Disc two), 2005; SR-15714; Floetry (Box 267)
          In same jacket as # SR-15713. Double album.
          Catalog # GEFF-11613-1; A-side Matrix # GEFR 11614-1 A ©
        - Floetry - Say yes (Remix), 2003; SR-15715; Floetry (Box 267)
          Catalog # DRMR-14090-1; A-side Matrix # DRMR-14090-1-A
          Dreamworks Records
        - Floren, Myron - Inspirational songs (Disc one), 1976; SR-15716; Floren, Myron (Box 267)
          In same jacket as # SR-15717. Double album.
          Catalog # R-7003; A-side Matrix # LPS-50329
          Ranwood Records, Inc
        - Floren, Myron - Inspirational songs (Disc two), 1976; SR-15717; Floren, Myron (Box 267)
          In same jacket as # SR-15716. Double album.
          Catalog # R-7003; A-side Matrix # LPS-50331
        - Meeno - I'm that n****; Vacant lot goes no limit, 2000; SR-15718; Meeno; Floss, Dave; Montané, Emoni (Box 267)
          Catalog # SPRO 81337; A-side Matrix # 81337-14 RE3-A
          Vacant Lot Records
        - Fludd, Travis - Have no doubts, 1988; SR-15719; Fludd, Travis (Box 267)
          Catalog # FMS 62315; A-side Matrix # FMS-62315-A
          Select Records
        - Fluke - Absurd, 1997; SR-15720; Fluke (Box 267)
          Catalog # YRTDJ 126; A-side Matrix # YRTDJ 126 B-01-01-1
          Circa
        - F.M. Inc. - Call me anytime, 1992; SR-15721; F.M. Inc. (Box 267)
          Catalog # NTD 002; A-side Matrix # NTD-002-A
          Nuff Tuff Music
        - Flying Lizards - Sex machine, 1984; SR-15722; Flying Lizards (Box 267)
          Catalog # TAK 19-12; A-side Matrix # TAK 1912 A-1U-1-1-2
          Statik Records
        - Flying Lizards - Money, 1979; SR-15723; Flying Lizards (Box 267)
          Catalog # DSKO 217; A-side Matrix # ST-DK-37820-1
          Virgin Records America, Inc.
        - Flyin Turkey - For Kim, 1993; SR-15724; Flyin Turkey (Box 267)
          Catalog # SI0050; A-side Matrix # SI-0050-A
          Spice Island Records
          Richmond Hill, New York
        - Fo' Clips - Be thankful, 1995; SR-15725; Fo' Clips (Box 267)